so this video is going to describe an
所以这段视频将描述一个
important property that some games have
一些游戏具有的重要属性
which is called dominant strategies to
这称为主导策略
begin with I'm going to start using this
首先，我将开始使用这个
word strategy that we haven't defined
我们尚未定义的单词策略
yet and indeed you're not going to get a
但是，实际上您不会得到
definition for a little while so to
定义了一段时间
begin with when I use the word strategy
从我使用策略一词开始
I want you to understand this just to
我想让你理解这只是为了
mean choosing some action this name in
意思是选择这个名称的动作
the end is going to be what we call a
最终将是我们所说的
pure strategy and it's going to turn out
纯粹的策略，结果将是
that there's another kind of strategy
还有另一种策略
that I haven't told you about yet and
我还没告诉过你
everything in this lecture is also going
这堂课的一切也在进行
to apply to that kind of strategy but
适用于这种策略，但
it's not going to matter for you right
对你来说没关系
now so let's just understand strategy to
现在，让我们只了解策略
mean choice of action so let's let Si
意味着选择行动，让我们让Si
and si prime be two different strategies
和si prime是两种不同的策略
that player I could take and let's let
我可以接受的球员，让我们
capital S - I be the set of all of the
大写S-我是所有
other things that everybody else could
其他人可以做的其他事情
do I'm going to define two different
我要定义两个不同的
definitions of what it means to say that
说那意味着什么的定义
si strip dominates s prime I so first we
si strip主导s素数，所以首先
have the notion of strict dominance and
有严格的统治地位的概念，
here I'm going to say that si strictly
在这里我要严格地说
dominates s prime I if it's the case
如果是的话，我会控制素数I
that for every other strategy profile of
对于其他所有战略概况
the other agents in other words for
换句话说，其他代理商
every other thing that they could do for
他们可以做的所有其他事情
every other joint set of actions that
其他所有联合行动
they could take the utility that player
他们可以利用那个球员
I gets when he plays si is more than the
当他玩si大于
utility that I gets when he plays s
他玩s时得到的实用程序
prime I so in other words it might
素我，换句话说，它可能
matter to player i what everybody else
对玩家而言很重要
does that might affect his utility but
会不会影响他的效用，但是
it will always be the case that he's
永远都是这样的
happier when he plays si then he is when
当他玩si时会更快乐
he plays s prime i and in fact he's
他打出了我的黄金杆，事实上他是
strictly happier because we have a
绝对快乐，因为我们有一个
strict inequality here so he's going to
严格的不平等，所以他要
get strictly more utility by playing
通过玩获得严格的更多效用
as I than by playing s-prime I that
因为我比起玩S-prime我
means that si strictly dominates s-prime
表示si严格控制s-prime
I now we have another notion of
我现在有另一个概念
dominance which I call very weak
我称自己为弱者
dominance it's almost the same
主导地位几乎是一样的
definition as you will have noticed the
您将注意到的定义
only difference here is that I have a
唯一的区别是我有一个
weak inequality instead of a strict
弱的不平等而不是严格的
inequality and so what this is saying is
不平等，这就是说
no matter what everybody else does I'm
不管我是谁
always at least as happy playing si as I
至少和我一样开心
am playing s Prime and when that's true
在玩Prime，那是真的
I say that si very weakly dominates as
我说si非常弱
Prime I now you might wonder why I have
总理我现在你可能想知道为什么我有
this name very weak that's because this
这个名字很弱是因为
condition even allows for equality so
条件甚至允许平等，所以
even if it's the case that si and s
即使是si和s
prime I are always exactly the same as
素数我总是和
each other I'm still allowed to say that
彼此，我仍然可以这样说
si si Prime and that sounds like a
si si Prime，听起来像是
strong thing to say about equality so we
关于平等有很强的话要说，所以我们
soften it by saying it's very weak
通过说它很弱来软化它
dominance now in fact there are also
其实现在也有优势
some other kinds of dominance that kind
其他的那种统治
of live in between these two that are
在这两个之间的生活
not quite as strong as strict dominance
不如严格的统治强
and not quite as weak as very weak
而不是非常虚弱
dominance but they're not important for
支配地位，但对于
us right now so I won't mention them
我们现在，所以我不会提及他们
well what is so important about
那么什么是重要的
dominance intuitively when a strategy
策略时直观地占据优势
when one strategy dominates another
当一种策略主导另一种
strategy then I don't really have to
策略，那么我真的不必
think about what the other agents are
考虑一下其他代理商
going to do in order to decide that I
去做决定我
prefer to play si than to play si prime
喜欢玩si而不是si prime
because I know that my utility is never
因为我知道我的工具永远不会
worse by playing si so regardless of the
玩si更糟，所以无论
kind of dominance it's sort of a good
占主导地位，这是一个很好的
idea for me just to play si now this can
现在我玩这个的想法对我来说可以
get even stronger if one strategy
如果一种策略变得更强大
dominates all of the other strategies in
支配着所有其他策略
that case then this one strategy si is
那么，这种策略si就是
kind of better than everything else and
比其他的都要好
in that case I can say not just that it
在那种情况下，我不仅可以说
dominates something but I can say that
占主导地位，但我可以说
its dominant that it's just kind of the
它的优势在于
best thing to do and if I have
最好的事情，如果我有
dominant-strategy then basically I don't
主导策略然后我基本上不
have to worry about what the other
不得不担心其他
agents are doing in the game at all I
代理商在游戏中所做的一切
can just play my dominant strategy and
可以发挥我的主导策略
that's going to be the best thing for me
对我来说那将是最好的
to do now formalizing that notion that
现在要做一个正式的概念
this is just the best thing to do I can
这只是我能做的最好的事情
notice I can claim to you and it's not
请注意，我可以向您索赔，但事实并非如此
hard to see that it's true that a
很难看出这是真的
strategy profile in which everybody is
每个人都在其中的战略概况
playing a dominant strategy has to be a
发挥主导策略必须是
Nash equilibrium so if everyone is
纳什均衡，所以如果每个人都
playing a dominant strategy then we've
扮演主导策略，那么我们已经
just got a Nash equilibrium because none
刚得到纳什均衡，因为没有
of us wants to change what we're doing
我们当中的人想要改变我们正在做的事情
we already know from the fact that the
我们已经从事实知道
strategy is dominant that there's
策略占主导地位
nothing better for me to do furthermore
没有什么比我更好的了
if we all have a strictly dominant
如果我们都有严格的统治地位
strategies then this equilibrium has got
策略，那么这个均衡就可以了
to be unique because there can't be two
独一无二，因为不可能有两个
equilibria in strictly dominant
严格占主导地位的均衡
strategies because that would mean we
策略，因为那意味着我们
prefer these strategies to each other
彼此更喜欢这些策略
strictly and that just can't happen so
严格地说，那样就不可能发生
lastly I want to think about the
最后我想想一下
prisoner's dilemma game and I want to
囚徒困境游戏，我想
argue to you that the players have a
跟你争辩说球员有一个
dominant strategy in this game so I want
这个游戏的主导策略，所以我想要
to claim to you that player one has the
声称您拥有一个玩家
dominant strategy of playing D and I'm
发挥D的主导策略，而我
going to do this by a case analysis so
通过案例分析来做到这一点
let's begin by considering the case
让我们从考虑情况开始
where player 2 plays see if player 2
玩家2在哪里玩，看看玩家2是否
plays C then player 1 is really thinking
玩C，那么玩家1真的在想
about this column of the matrix he knows
关于他知道的矩阵的这一列
he's in this column and that means he
他在此专栏中，这意味着他
faces a choice between getting a payoff
在获得回报之间面临选择
of minus 1 and getting a payoff of 0 and
减去1并得到0的收益
0 is bigger than minus 1 and so player 1
0比负1大，因此玩家1
would prefer to get 0 which means that
宁愿得到0，这意味着
his best response to C is to play D on
他对C的最佳反应是在D上打D
the other hand let's consider the case
另一方面让我们考虑一下情况
where player 2 is playing D in this case
在这种情况下，玩家2在玩D
player 1 finds himself in this green
玩家1发现自己处于绿色状态
column and that's kind of too bad for
专栏，对于
him because now he faces a choice
他，因为现在他面临选择
between the payoff of minus 4 and a
在负4的收益和a之间
payoff of minus 3 and both of these
减去-3的回报
numbers are smaller than the numbers
数字小于数字
that he had a choice about before so he
他以前可以选择
likes the blue color
喜欢蓝色
better than he likes the green column
比他喜欢绿色的专栏要好
but if he is in the green column he
但是如果他在绿色栏中，
still prefers to get -3 than to get -4
仍然比得到-4更喜欢得到-3
and that means in this case he again
这意味着在这种情况下，他再次
prefers to play D so we can see that
喜欢玩D，所以我们可以看到
regardless of what player 2 does player
不管玩家2做什么
1 best response by playing D and in both
同时播放D和D均可获得最佳响应
cases his preference was strict and that
情况下他的偏爱很严格，那
means he has a strictly dominant
表示他有严格的统治地位
strategy in this case and so D is a
这种情况下的策略，所以D是一个
dominant strategy here I'll leave it to
主导策略，我将其留给
you to see that the same thing is true
你看到同样的事情是真的
if I argue that player 2 has a dominant
如果我认为玩家2具有主导地位
strategy of playing D and I do a case
我玩D游戏的策略
analysis about what player 1 can do but
关于玩家1可以做什么的分析
the game is symmetric so the same
游戏是对称的，所以相同
argument goes through there as well
争论也在那里